the purpose of this short video is to
这部短片的目的是
show how to set up the IntelliJ IDEA
显示如何设置IntelliJ IDEA
development environment for skaaland
skaaland的开发环境
development prerequisites are that you
发展的前提是你
already have a suitable Java development
已经有合适的Java开发
kit or Java SDK for your platform and an
套件或适用于您平台的Java SDK，以及
installation of IntelliJ IDEA itself
IntelliJ IDEA本身的安装
we're using the community edition here
我们在这里使用社区版
first thing after launch is to check for
启动后的第一件事是检查
updates and here we're good to go and
更新，在这里我们很好
the next step is to install the required
下一步是安装所需的
plugins so we'll go to preferences we'll
插件，因此我们将转到首选项
scroll down to plugins and browse the
向下滚动到插件并浏览
repositories the first plug-in we'll
存储库我们将使用的第一个插件
grab is not strictly required but will
抓取不是严格要求的，但会
be using big bucket a lot so let's grab
经常使用大桶，所以让我们抓住
that one right click download and
右键点击下载，
install
安装
and the next one is the Scala plug-in
下一个是Scala插件
itself click on that one right click
本身就单击该鼠标右键
download and install this is a somewhat
下载并安装这有点
longer download so the assumption is
下载时间更长，因此假设是
that you would have closed the
你会关闭
repository browser for the plugins and
插件的存储库浏览器和
then allowed the IDE to restart and the
然后允许IDE重新启动，并且
next step is to create a new project and
下一步是创建一个新项目，
we will want an SBT project SBT is Scala
我们想要一个SBT项目SBT是Scala
simple build tool which allows us to
简单的构建工具，使我们能够
create a project with room to grow in
创建一个有成长空间的项目
terms of external dependencies and we'll
外部依赖项的条款，我们将
put this in a suitable place in our
放在我们合适的地方
directory hierarchy and hit finish and
目录层次结构，并完成
we can close the tooltip and the first
我们可以关闭工具提示和第一个
thing to do is to create a suitable
要做的是创建一个合适的
source directory by clicking on the
通过单击
hello project node new directory and we
你好项目节点新目录，我们
can create the entire hierarchy source
可以创建整个层次结构源
main Scala in one step and when you do
一步一步完成主Scala
this the first time the Scala directory
这是Scala目录的第一次
might not show up in light blue yet so
可能不会以浅蓝色显示
you'll probably want to wait until that
您可能要等到那
happens and then right-click new and
发生，然后右键单击“新建”，然后
choose Scala class if you don't see
如果看不到，请选择Scala类
Scala class you will need to wait a
Scala类，您将需要等待
little longer until it processes the
直到它处理
plugin and indexes the jars that belong
插件并索引属于的jar
to the plugins so let's say we'll create
插件，所以假设我们将创建
the Scala class will actually want an
Scala类实际上需要一个
object and let's call that hello and
对象，让我们打个招呼，
we'll turn that into the simplest
我们将把它变成最简单的
possible Scala app so we'll add here
可能的Scala应用程序，因此我们将在此处添加
extends app and put as
扩展应用程序并放置为
the body println hello and we should be
身体println你好，我们应该
good to go so now let's try to run this
很好，所以现在让我们尝试运行此
app by right-clicking on hello and we
右键点击您好，我们
don't yet see an item to do that that's
还没有看到可以做到这一点的项目
because we still need to add a JDK so
因为我们仍然需要添加一个JDK这样
let's go to file project structure and
让我们转到文件项目结构，
we see here that there isn't a project
我们在这里看到没有一个项目
SDK so what we want to do if you don't
SDK，如果您不这样做，我们该怎么办
see a valid SDK here in this drop-down
在此下拉列表中查看有效的SDK
we will want to create a new an entry
我们将要创建一个新条目
for a new Java 6 SDK and we will want to
对于新的Java 6 SDK，我们将希望
navigate to the corresponding Java home
导航到相应的Java主页
on your machine so in case of the Mac it
在您的计算机上，因此在Mac上
would be Java a home and let's try that
将是Java的家，让我们尝试一下
and that gives us the default 1.6 Java
这为我们提供了默认的1.6 Java
SDK on the Mac let's look at these
Mac上的SDK让我们看看这些
errors that will be fixed after we apply
应用后将修复的错误
this change and now it's reindex in some
这种变化，现在它在某些地方重新索引
of the jars
罐子里
and we should now be good to go so
现在我们应该很好走
right-click again and indeed now it says
再次右键单击，实际上现在它说
run hello
打个招呼
let's try that and there's a little
让我们尝试一下，有一点
error and this is a bug in the Scala
错误，这是Scala中的错误
plugin as far as I can tell and that
据我所知，该插件
workaround is to create the missing
解决方法是创建丢失的
output directory manually the first time
第一次手动输出目录
so we'll create as it says down here a
所以我们将按照下面的说明进行创建
target slash scallop 2.10 slash classes
目标斜线扇贝2.10斜线类
so hello new directory target Scala - 2
所以您好新目录目标Scala-2
. n slash classes there might be another
。 n个斜杠类，可能还有另一个
error message that we can probably
我们可能会出现的错误消息
ignore let's check and try running hello
忽略让我们检查并尝试运行你好
again
再次
and it worked here we go
它在这里起作用了
all right so we successfully created a
好的，我们成功创建了一个
very simple Scala app project and we're
非常简单的Scala应用项目，我们
able to execute that project so this
能够执行该项目，所以这
workaround is necessary only the first
解决方法仅在第一时间是必要的
time you set the project up okay one
你建立项目的时间还可以
other thing I want to illustrate is
我想说明的另一件事是
Scala worksheets which are useful
有用的Scala工作表
mechanism for just playing around with
玩转的机制
code before you make it part of an
代码，然后再使其成为
actual app or library so we can create a
实际的应用程序或库，因此我们可以创建一个
new Scala worksheet and we'll just call
新的Scala工作表，我们将仅致电
it hello - and here we can just write
你好-在这里我们可以写
some Java code so for example Val X is 3
一些Java代码，例如Val X为3
and then X and now we can say run
然后是X，现在我们可以说运行
and it just execute all the code on the
它只是执行所有的代码
worksheet so you see here that it was
工作表，所以您在这里看到它是
able to define X and then to evaluate X
能够定义X然后评估X
it just evaluates that expression and
它只是评估该表达式，
returns the resulting value so if we
返回结果值，所以如果我们
change the expression we can re-execute
更改表达式，我们可以重新执行
the worksheet and alum update that
工作表和明矾更新
expression accordingly so we can
相应地表达，所以我们可以
probably have multiple expressions here
可能在这里有多个表达式
let's try that yep so basically you know
让我们尝试一下，所以基本上你知道
you can keep modifying this and
您可以继续修改它，
experimenting and once your code
实验一下，一旦你的代码
fragments are ready to be incorporated
准备将片段合并
into the actual project you can just
进入实际项目，您可以
copy and paste those okay so that's it
复制并粘贴这些就可以了
for now I think this will help you get
现在，我认为这将帮助您获得
started and we'll be back with some more
开始，我们会再回来的
advanced stuff sometime soon
很快就会有进阶的东西